(Amy:)The kind who almost put a pillow
over your face last night.
(Sheldon:)Wow.
(Sheldon:)I anticipated
we'd have problems,
(Sheldon:)but I never thought your
scientific rigor would be one of them.
(Amy:)I'm sorry, are you questioning
my integrity as a scientist?
(Sheldon:)If the lab room
disposable shoe cover fits.
(Penny:)Was that a science diss?
(Bernadette:)- Yeah.
- Was it a good one?
- Eh.
- Ah.
(Amy:)What would a
theoretical physicist
(Amy:)understand about an
experiment anyway?
(Amy:)I mean, you wouldn't know
a confounding variable
(Amy:)if two of them hit you in
the face at the same time!
(Amy:)And you don't even
get that joke,
(Amy:)'cause you don't even work
with confounding variables!
(Sheldon:)How dare you?
(Amy:)Oh, you heard me.
Your experimental bona fides
(Amy:)are laughable.
(Sheldon:)Whoa, whoa! Now you're
making fun of my bona fides?
(Amy:)Can't make fun of something
that's a null set.
(Leonard:)I feel like
I should say "damn."
- Do it.
Damn!
(Sheldon:)Well, if you are so protective
of the scientific method,
(Sheldon:)perhaps we should use
the next five weeks
(Sheldon:)to finish what we started.
Well, for science, maybe I will!
For science, maybe you should!
- Fine!
(Leonard:)- Good.
- Great.
(Amy:)Do you want to go to our place
and make out?
(Sheldon:)Does Stephen Hawking roll
through the quad?
The new neighbors
are weird.